littlecoffeefox.com 2019-07-17

# Privacy Policy for Littlecoffeefox.com | LittleCoffeeFox

**Last Updated** on: May 24, 2018

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Littlecoffeefox.com (hereinafter “Little Coffee Fox”), a Roaming Fox Media, LLC website, is opposed to unauthorized commercial emails, or spam.  Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or would like to report spam, please send an email to privacy@littlecoffeefox.com

 **What personal information do we collect?**

 _Voluntarily Submitted Information_ : From time to time, we may collect personal information, such as your name or email address. For instance, you may voluntarily provide this information to Little Coffee Fox when you subscribe to a newsletter, enroll in a free course or live event, sign up to access a free resource, leave a comment, or submit a contact form.

 _Information Collected by a Third-Party_ : Occasionally, Little Coffee Fox may receive information about you from a third party. For example, if you use a software on Little Coffee Fox provided by a third party that information may be transferred to Little Coffee Fox for our use.

 _Automatically-Collected Information:_ When you visit Little Coffee Fox some information will be automatically collecting. This information includes the time of your visit, your IP address at the time of your visit, your operating system, the type of device you use, referring website, pages you viewed, and action you took while using Little Coffee Fox.

 _Use of Cookies_ : Little Coffee Fox may log information using cookies. A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

 **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you take a variety of actions on Little Coffee Fox; the following are some examples of situations that we may collect information and the type of information we collect.

 _Electronic Newsletter_ : When registering to receive our electronic newsletter we require the following information: (i) Name, and (ii) e-mail address. This information will be used to send electronic communications to you via email.

 _Contact Forms:_ When contacting Little Coffee Fox for any purpose, we utilize numerous forms throughout our site. These forms require the following information: (i) Name, and (ii) e-mail address. Other information may be voluntarily given on these forms, but are not required. This information will be used to respond to your inquiry.

 _Purchases Made on Little Coffee Fox_ : When you make a purchase on Little Coffee Fox, we use a third-party online checkout system, this system is described in-depth below. To process your purchase, certain information is required, including address, e-mail address and credit card information. All transactions are secured via SSL encryption and credit card information will never be transferred via email or other unsecured means.

 **How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested;
  * To improve our website to better serve you;
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature;
  * To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products;
  * To send you promotional information, such as a newsletter or other informational information. Each email will provide instructions on how to opt-out of future communications;
  * To send administrative communications, such as confirmation of e-mail address, and updates to policies ;
  * To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries);
  * To provide user support;
  * To process payment for transactions made on Little Coffee Fox; or,
  * To notify you of new information or services that may be of interest to you.

 **We use cookies to:**

  * Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.
  * Keep track of advertisements.
  * Serve advertisements, covered more below.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.
  * You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser’s “Help Menu” to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
  * If you turn cookies off, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.

 **Third-party disclosure:**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.

However, Little Coffee Fox may use third-party service. How each third-party service provider uses your personal information is dictated by their own privacy policy. Currently, Little Coffee Fox uses the following third-party service providers:

 _Email Marketing_ : Little Coffee Fox uses Convertkit as its email service provider. Convertkit collects contact information, distributes our mass email communications, and tracks your actions taken when interacting with those emails.

Emails sent via Convertkit contain tracking pizes that allow us to analyze the effectiveness of this emails. This allows us to see what emails you open and which links you click in an email. All data related to email marketing is stored on Convertkit’s servers. You can view Convertkit’s complete privacy policy [here](https://convertkit.com/privacy/).

Occasionally we may rely on the third-party services, HelloBar and Leadpages, to service certain opt-in systems and landing pages. All information collected by HelloBar and Leadpages are passed directly to Convertkit and not stored by any party than Convertkit.

See Leadpage’s privacy policy [here](https://www.leadpages.net/privacy), and HelloBar’s privacy policy [here](https://www.hellobar.com/privacy-policy/).

 _Tracking_ : Little Coffee Fox uses marketing tools that help us improve user’s experience when visiting our site. These tools allow us to view aggregated data and to run tests to determine which pages may be performing best. Any personally identifiable information acquired by these tools will not be used by the tools. Currently, Little Coffee Fox uses the following third-party tracking service providers:

Google Analytics: [Privacy policy](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245)

 _Remarketing_ : Little Coffee Fox uses remarketing cookies and conversion pixels from Facebook and Google to present offers to you for our products or conduct over Google’s content network and social media networks. This means that you may see an ad for Little Coffee Fox after visiting our websites. Additionally, Little Coffee Fox creates custom audiences consisting of email subscribers and customers to present offers to you via social media networks. You may opt-out of our remarketing practices below:

Facebook: [opt-out of remarketing](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217)

Google: [opt-out or remarketing](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en)

 _Purchases:_ Little Coffee Fox uses SamCart to process purchases. SamCart processes the order and collects personal information. SamCart collects your name, email address, and payment information. All payment information is stored on SamCart’s servers. You can see SamCart’s privacy policy [here](https://www.samcart.com/privacy-policy/).

SamCart processes payments using Paypal and Stripe. These services store your name, amount of your purchases, and payment information on their servers. You can see Paypal’s privacy policy [here](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full), and Stripe’s privacy policy [here](https://stripe.com/us/privacy/).

Information provided during the checkout process may be passed to Convertkit to allow us to contact you in the future or provide you with offers to other products. Additionally, information may be passed to Teachable to create a username and password. The information passed to Teachable will include your name and email address, but Teachable will receive none of your payment information. This information is provided to Teachable to allow you to access any online courses you have purchased on Little Coffee Fox. All usernames and passwords are stored on Teachable’s servers. You can see Teachable’s privacy policy [here](https://teachable.com/privacy-policy).

 _Surveys_ : Occasionally, we may provide you the option to complete a voluntary survey. These surveys will be provided by SurveyMonkey. All data submitted to SurveyMonkey is stored on their servers. You can see SurveyMonkey’s privacy policy [here](https://www.surveymonkey.com/mp/legal/privacy-policy/).

 _Webinars_ : Little Coffee Fox will periodically host webinars. These webinars will be hosted through Genesis Digital. If you voluntarily register for a webinar, you will be required to submit personal information, such as name and email address. This information is then transferred to Convertkit and may be used to market products and services to you. Additionally, information submitted to Genesis Digital is stored on their servers. You can see Genesis Digital’s privacy policy [here](https://www.genesisdigital.co/_legal/privacypolicy.php).

 **Advertising Privacy Statement:**

 _Adthrive_ : Little Coffee Fox is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behavior on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third-party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by going [here](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism [here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

 _European Economic Area Residents_ : If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact AdThrive at [info@adthrive.com](mailto:info@adthrive.com). If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences icon. (Available in the EU only.)

 _Amazon Affiliate Program_ : We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

 **Third-party links:**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Personal Data Rights:**

 _Opt-out_ : You may opt-out of any future email communications by following the unsubscribe links at the bottom of every email. Additionally, you may notify us at privacy@littlecoffeefox.com to be removed from our mailing list.

 _Accessing Your Data_ : You may access any personal information we have stored about you by submitting a request to privacy@littlecoffeefox.com.

 _Amend_ : If you would like to amend your personal information for any reason you can contact us at privacy@littlecoffeefox.com.

 _Forget_ : You have a right to be forgotten. Therefore, you can request that we erase any personal data that we have regarding you by emailing us at privacy@littlecoffeefox.com.

 **Sale of Business or Assets:**

In the event that the Site or substantially all of its assets is sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, the information we have collected about you may be one of the assets sold or merged in connection with that transaction.

 **Changes to Privacy Policy:**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on the Site, with the “Effective Date” posted at the top of the Policy. We may revise and update this Privacy Policy if our practices change, as technology changes, or as we add new services or change existing ones. If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy or how we handle your personal information, or we are going to use any personal information in a manner that is materially different from that stated in our Privacy Policy at the time we collected such information, we will give you a reasonable opportunity to consent to the change. If you do not consent, your personal information will be used as agreed to under the terms of the privacy policy in effect at the time we obtained that information. By using our Site or services after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to our then-current privacy policy. We will use information previously obtained in accordance with the Privacy Policy in effect when the information was obtained from you.

 **For more information contact:**

Jon Abrahamsen

privacy@littlecoffeefox.com

### Enter the Fox Den Resource Library

Subscribe now to get access to 40+ pages of free journal printables, brush lettering worksheets, video tutorials, and tons more!
